Guide to the John Bennett Tuck papers, 1890-1948.
Tuck, John Bennet papers, 1890-1948.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
John Bennett Tuck papers, 1890-1948.
2604
John Bennett Tuck, 1868-1955.
8.6 cubic ft.
Student papers, estate records, military records, correspondence, family papers, and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes papers written when he was a student at Cornell University; estate records with material relating to the F. P. Collins Company, Dey Brothers, Milmac, Inc., and the Mowat Company; military records of his activities in the Spanish-American War, the New York National Guard, and World War I; and correspondence, notes, and other items concerning his association with the American Foundation, the American Legion, the Association Against the Prohibition Amendment, Cornell University Trustees, the Cornell Law Association, the Guards of Liberty, and the Young Workers League of America; also, family papers referring largely to the sale of the Tuck farm in Ogdensburg, New York, and three letters (1917-1918) from his brother Charles H. Tuck which describe the Russian Revolution of 1917 and Far Eastern affairs from his vantage point as an import agent in Harbin, Manchuria. Includes 19 maps of trenches and towns in France and Belgium during World War 1.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Lawyer; Cornell University Class of 1893; Cornell University Alumni Trustee, 1930-1935.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes papers written when he was a student at Cornell University; estate records with material relating to the F. P. Collins Company, Dey Brothers, Milmac, Inc., and the Mowat Company; military records of his activities in the Spanish-American War, the New York National Guard, and World War I; and correspondence, notes, and other items concerning his association with the American Foundation, the American Legion, the Association Against the Prohibition Amendment, Cornell University Trustees, the Cornell Law Association, the Guards of Liberty, and the Young Workers League of America; also, family papers referring largely to the sale of the Tuck farm in Ogdensburg, New York, and three letters (1917-1918) from his brother Charles H. Tuck which describe the Russian Revolution of 1917 and Far Eastern affairs from his vantage point as an import agent in Harbin, Manchuria. Includes 19 maps of trenches and towns in France and Belgium during World War 1.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Tuck, John Bennett, 1868-1955.; Tuck, Charles H.; American Foundation.; American Legion.; Association Against the Prohibition Amendment.; Cornell Law Association.; Cornell University.; Dey Brothers.; F. P. Collins Company.; Guards of Liberty.; Milmac, Inc.; Mowat Company.; New York (State). National Guard.; Young Workers League of America.
Subjects:
Spanish-American War, 1898--Veterans--United States.; World War, 1914-1918--Veterans--United States.; Prohibition.
Places:
Soviet Union--History--Revolution, 1917-1921.; East Asia.; Harbin (Manchuria).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Brown, Howard K. (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
- Cranwell Estate, Elizabeth Fenn - Judicial Statement (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Dey, Donald Mitchell - Estate of, Lipe Trust Mortgage (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
- Dey, Donald Mitchell, Mrs. - General File (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Dey, Donald Mitchell - Claims (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Dey, Donald Mitchell - Fayetteville Commercial Bank (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Dey, Donald Mitchell - Inheritance Tax (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Dey - Estate of Mary (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Daugherty, James C. (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
- Fitzgibbons, Catherine - Last Will and Testament (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Haas, Barbara - Last Will and Testament (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Kelley, George G.B. - Estate of (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Kelley, George G.B. - Inheritance Taxes (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Linehan, Daniel J. (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Lucey, Dennis B. - Estate of (Box 1, Folder 19-22)
- McCarthy, Anna V. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- McCarthy, Dennis Percy - General (Box 2, Folder 2)
- McCarthy, Dennis Percy - Estate of (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
- McFarland, William J.R. - Estate of (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
- Merrick, Mrs. Charlotte Day (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Milmac Inc. - General (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Mooney, Edward L. - Estate of (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
- Meunch, William - Estate of (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
- O'Connor, Mary A. - Estate of (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Peck, Anna L. (Cary) - General (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
- Peck, Anna L. (Cary) - Judicial Settlement (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Peck, Anna L. (Cary) - The Adirondack Arrow Inc. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Peck, Anna L. (Cary) - Eagle Bay Property (Box 2, Folder 18-20)
- Peck, Anna L. (Cary) - Armstrong, Gwendolyn B. Claim (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Peck, Fanny F. Trust (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
- Peck, Fanny F. Trust (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- Robertson, Edward - Will of (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
- Tuck, Andrew - Estate of (Box 3, Folder 5-7)
- Tuck, Estate of Andrew E. II (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Tuck, John B. - the Chalet, The Gate House, Eagle Bay Property (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Watts, Herbert C. - Will of (Box 3, Folder 10)
- White, Estate of M. Thersa (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Military, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
- Military and Personal, 1916-1917 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Military, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
- Army Staff College - 3rd Course, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 18-20)
- Correspondence and Papers, 1891-1921 (Box 4)
- Correspondence and Papers, 1921-1922 (Box 5)
- Correspondence and Papers, 1925-1931 (Box 6)
- Correspondence and Papers, 1929-1943 (Box 7)
- Correspondence and Papers, 1941-1946 (Box 7)
- Correspondence and Papers; also photographs, 1941-1946 (Box 8)
- College course notes (Box 9)
- Scrapbook (Box 9)
- Delta Epsilon Song Book (Box 9)
- Thesis (Box 9)
- Ledger (Box 9)
- '93 Sourvenir Book (Box 9)
- A.E.F. class book, 1918 (Box 9)
- Cornell material, letter from David Hoy, exams, papers, and speeches. Speech topics include Delta Upsilon, Freshmen banquet, Co-education, experiences with a general store, in a dentist chair, military, alumni association, James R. Fuller eulogy, papers on Benedict Arnold and other historical figures., ca. 1890 (Box 10)
- Maps of France, Paris, Metz, others, World War I era, ca. 1915 (Box 11)
- Photograph - group, not identified (Folder 1)
- Certificates
  - Army Commission, 1898 (Folder 1)
  - Awards, 1911, 1917 (Folder 1)
  - National Guard Commissions, 1907, 1913, 1917 (Folder 1)